Mss.B.L493
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence, 7.0 Linear feet 17 upright boxes, 1 oversized folder, 1 digital record. (Box 1-17)
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, April, 1875; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
    [Paris, ca.] A.L.S. 4p. In French. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, Philadelphia, May 1, 1875; 8x5; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910
    Cambridge, Mass., A.L.S. 2p.and add.,end. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning the museum of comparative zoology. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Philadelphia, May 1, 1875; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910
    Cambridge, Mass., A.L.S. 3p.and add.,end. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning his donation of coleoptera collection to the museum, and how the museum will be able to take care of it. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], May 3, 1875; 4 1/2" x 7"; Sharp, David, 1840-1922
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, May 7, 1875; 5" x 8"; Coues, Elliott, 1842-1899
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to John L. LeConte, May 10, 1875; 7-3/4 x 9-3/4; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, Philadelphia, May 15, 1875; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910
    Cambridge, Mass., A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Is pleased with his decision to place his coleoptera in the museum. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], May 19, 1875; 5" x 8"; Coues, Elliott, 1842-1899
  - Letter to [J.L.] Leconte, May 24, 1875; 5" x 8"; Osten-Sacken, C. R. (Carl Robert), 1828-1906
  - Letter to J.L. Leconte, May 25, 1875; 5" x 8"; Dall, William Healey, 1845-1927
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, May 29, 1875; 5" x 8"; Hinckley, Isaac, 1815-1888
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, June 18, 1875; 5 1/2" x 8 1/2"; Riley, Charles V., (Charles Valentine), 1843-1895
    On board the Abyssinia, A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte ?], July 13, 1875; 5" x 8"; Guyot, A. (Arnold), 1807-1884
    Princeton, N.J., A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, Aug. 2, 1875; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    Staten Island, A.L.S. 2p.and add. (see Le Conte papers.) Asks for information for a committee. Originally B L493.3
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, Aug. 15, 1875; 7x4-1/2; Dana, James Dwight, 1813-1895
    New Haven, A.L.S. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.) Will publish his address.
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, Aug. 18, 1875; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Hopes to meet with him and several others in Philadelphia. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Aug. 20, 1875; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], Aug. 20, 1875
  - Letter to the Commission on "Cow-hair" goods, National Academy of Sciences, Aug. 28, 1875; 13x8; Schaeffer, E. M.
    Philadelphia, L.S.: E.M.Schaeffer and J.G.Hunt. 9p. and end. Copy. (see Le Conte papers.)
  - [Address as retiring president of the American association for the advancement of science,], August, 1875; 7 3/4" x 11 3/4"; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Detroit meeting, A.D. 25 leaves Printed: AAAS, Proceedings, v.24,1876.
  - Members ticket for John L. Le Conte, Aug., 1875; 2-3/4x4-1/4, encased in protective coating; American Association for the Advancement of Science
    Removed for exhibit to AAAS, 15 Jan. 1998 item returned in good order, 1/22/99
    Detroit, D.S. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.)
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Sept. 2, 1875; 5" x 8"; Hubbard, H. G., (Henry Guernsey), 1850-1899
    Detroit, A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to J.[L. ] Le Conte, Sept. 6, 1875; 4 1/2" x 7 1/4"; Woodward, Joseph Janvier, 1833-1884
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, Sept. 15, 1875; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Cheveult, A.
    Mariposa, Cal., A.L.S. 2p.,end. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Hopes to study the insects of California.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Sept. 13, 1875; 5" x 8"; Hagen, Hermann August, 1817-1893
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Sept. 14, 1875; 4 3/4" x 7"; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Sept. 16, 1875; 5" x 3"; Dana, James Dwight, 1813-1895
    New Haven, Postal card. 1p. and add.
  - Letter to Joseph Henry, Washington, Sept. 17, 1875; 13x8; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Washington, L.S.: John L. Le Conte and J.J.Woodward. 11p.and end. (see Le Conte paper Report on "Cow-hair" goods.
  - Letter to Joseph Henry, Washington, Sept. 17, 1875; 13x8; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Washington, L.S.: John L. Le Conte and J.J. Woodward. 2p.and end. Copy. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning their report on "cow-hair" goods.
  - Letter to Joseph Henry, Sept. 20, 1875; 10x8; Bristow, Benjamin Helm, 1832-1896
    Washington, L. 2p. Copy. (see Le Conte papers.) Thanks for report on "cow-hair" goods.
  - Letter to J.[L.] Le Conte, Sept. 22, 1875; 4 1/2" x 7 1/4"; Woodward, Joseph Janvier, 1833-1884
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], Sept. 25, 1875
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], Sept. 28, 1875; 8x5; Schwartz, Eugene Amandus, 1844-1928
    Detroit, A.L.S. 3p.,end. (see Le Conte papers.) News on entomology of the U.S.
  - Letter to Jo[h]n L. Le Conte, Oct. 2, 1875; 9x5-1/2; American Public Health Association
    New York, A.L.S.: Elisha Harris. 2p.,end. (see Le Conte papers.) Asks for title of his paper.
  - Letter to J.[L.] Le Conte, Oct. 5, 1875; 4 1/2" x 7 1/4"; Woodward, Joseph Janvier, 1833-1884
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Oct. 8, 1875; 5" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Oct. 10, 1875; 5" x 8"; Gabb, William More, 1839-1878
  - Letter to J.[L.] Le Conte, Oct. 17, 1875; 5" x 8"; Hubbard, H. G., (Henry Guernsey), 1850-1899
    Detroit, A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to John [L. Le Conte], Oct. 21, 1875; 5" x 8"; Rogers, Fairman, 1833-1900
    Newport, A.L.S. 1p.
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. Le Conte, Philadelphia, Oct. 27, 1875; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Smithsonian Institution.
    Washington, L.S.: Joseph Henry. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning the Treasury's decision on calf-hair goods.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Nov. 17, 1875; 5" x 8"; Dow, John M.
    Philadelphia A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, Nov. 23, 1875; 5" x 8"; Youmans, William Jay, 1838-1901
    New York, A.L.S. 1p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. LeConte, Dec. 24, 1875; Andrews, W. V.
  - Letter to Joseph Henry, Washington, Dec. 24, 1875; 13x5; Burnam, Curtis Field, 1877-
    Washington, L. 4p.and end. Copy. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning Le Conte's, etc., report on "cow-hair" studies.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Dec. 24, 1875; 5" x 8"; Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1837-1911
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Dec. 30, 1875; 5" x 8"; Schwartz, Eugene Amandus, 1844-1928
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 3p. In German. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Dec. 30, 1875; 5" x 8"; Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1837-1911
  - Letter to Joseph Henry, Dec. 31, 1875; 13x8; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Washington, L. 6p. Copy. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning the report on "cew-hair" fabrics.
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, Dec. 31, 1875; 9-1/2x7-1/4; Woodward, Joseph Janvier, 1833-1884
    Washington, D.C., L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Forwards material on the report Henry sent him on the calf-hair goods.
  - Concerning the report on cow-hair goods, [1875]; 12-1/2x8; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    A.D. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.) Refers to Woodward.
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, Jan. 5, 1876; 6-3/4x4-1/2; Rudder, William, b. 1820
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Thanks him for his publication and compliments him on it. Offers, in return, a publication of his own.
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, Jan. 5, 1876; 8x5-1/4; Woodward, Joseph Janvier, 1833-1884
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Has, with Henry's approval, arranged for their report on "cow-hair" fabrics to be printed.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Jan. 13, 1876; 5" x 8"; Belfrage, G. W.
    Clifton, Texas, A.L.S. 3p.
  - Letter to Joseph Henry, Jan. 15, 1876; 13x8; Bristow, Benjamin Helm, 1832-1896
    Washington; L.S. 1p.and end. Enc.of 3p. Copy. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning the customs and instructions for handling cow-hair goods.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Jan. 24, 1876; 5 1/4" x 8 1/2"; Putnam, F. W., (Frederic Ward), 1839-1915
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, Jan. 26, 1876; 5" x 8"; Genth, F. A. (Frederick Augustus), 1820-1893
    University of Pennsylvania, A.L.S. 1p.
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], Jan. 26, 1876; 8x5; Harvard University. Museum of Comparative Zoology
    L.S.: Abbott Lawrence, Secy. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Thanks for his donation of coleoptera. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Feb. 3, 1876; 6 1/4" x 7 3/4"; Grote, Augustus Radcliffe, 1841-1903
  - Letter to J.L. Leconte, Feb. 3, 1876; 4 1/2" x 7"; Whiteaves, Joseph Frederick, 1835-1909
    Montreal, A.L.S. 4p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Feb. 12, 1876; 5" x 8"; Belfrage, G. W.
    Clifton, Texas, A.L.S. 3p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Feb. 15, 1876; 4 1/2" x 7"; Whiteaves, Joseph Frederick, 1835-1909
    Montreal, A.L.S. 4p. End. by J.L.Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Feb. 22, 1876; 5" x 8"; Sharp, David, 1840-1922
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, Feb. 23, 1876; 5" x 8"; Blodget, Lorin, 1823-1901
    A.L.S. 1p. Mentions A.P.S.
  - Letter to Jno. L. Leconte, Feb. 28, 1876; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Bickmore, Albert S. (Albert Smith), 1839-1914
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, March 1, 1876; 4 3/4" x 7"; Stillé, Charles J. (Charles Janeway), 1819-1899
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. Le Conte, March 2, 1876; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Campbell, J. S.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.) Asks that he sign and return the enclosed minutes [wanting] so that he might present them to the APS.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, March 2, 1876; 8" x 10"; Cox, E. T. (Edward Travers), 1821-1907
    Indianapolis, A.L.S. 1p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, Philadelphia, March 10, 1876; 9x5-3/4; Brugsch, Heinrich, 1827-1894
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Asks for information on the scarabs of ancient Egypt. B L493.3
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, March 16, 1876; 5" x 8"; Hagen, Hermann August, 1817-1893
  - Letter to John [L. Le Conte], March 21, 1876; 5" x 8"; LeConte, Joseph, 1823-1901
    Oakland, Cal., A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], March 23, 1876; 5" x 8"; Hagen, Hermann August, 1817-1893
  - Letter to J.L. Leconte, April 4, 1876; 4 1/2" x 7"; Sharp, David, 1840-1922
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], April 6, 1876; 4 1/2" x 7"; Sharp, David, 1840-1922
    Thornhill, A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, Philadelphia, April 12, 1876; 9x5-3/4; Bey, H. Brugsen
    A.L.S. 2p.and add. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning affairs at the Centennial Exhibition.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, April 12, 1876; 5" x 8"; Putnam, F. W., (Frederic Ward), 1839-1915
  - Letter to J.[L.] Le Conte, April 14, 1876; 5" x 8"; Barnard, Frederick A. P. (Frederick Augustus Porter), 1809-1889
    New York, L. 4p.
  - Invitation to John L. Le Conte to the opening of the new building, April 22, 1876; 6-1/2x5-1/4; Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts.
    Printed D.filled in in ms. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.)
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], April 24, 1876; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Putzeÿs, Jules, 1809-1882
    Brussels, A.L.S. 2p. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Introduces a collector of insects. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to J.L. Leconte, April 25, 1876; 5" x 8"; Barnard, Frederick A. P. (Frederick Augustus Porter), 1809-1889
  - Letter to John [L. Le Conte], May 4, 1876; 5" x 8"; LeConte, Joseph, 1823-1901
    Oakland, Cal., A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, May 4, [1876]; 4 1/2" x 7"; Matthews, A. (Andrew), 1815-1897
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, May 11, 1876; 5" x 8"; Hagen, Hermann August, 1817-1893
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], May 16, 1876; 4 1/2" x 7"; Sharp, David, 1840-1922
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, May 24, 1876; 4" x 6 3/4"; Price, Eli K., (Eli Kirk), 1797-1884
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], May 26, 1876; 5" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to J.L. Leconte, May 27, 1876; 5" x 8"; Behrens, James
    San Francisco, A.L.S. 1p.
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. Le Conte, Philadelphia, June 4, 1876; 8x5; Greet, Ferdinand
    A.L.S. 4p.,end. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning entomological publications to and from England to the U.S. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to J.L. Leconte, June 17, 1876; 5" x 8"; Hubbard, H. G., (Henry Guernsey), 1850-1899
    Detroit, A.L.S. 3p.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, June 24, 1876; 5" x 8"; Thomson, James
  - Letter to John [L. Le Conte], July 1, 1876; 5" x 8"; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    Boston, A.L.S. 3p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, July 3, 1876; 5" x 8"; Thomson, James
    Greene co., New York, A.L.S. 4p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, July 5, 1876; 5" x 8"; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    [Boston] A.L.S. 1p.
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], July 10, 1876; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Candèze, E. C. (Ernest Charles), 1827-1898
    A.L.S. 3p.,end. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Entomology.
  - Letter to J.L. Leconte, Aug. 10, 1876; 4 1/2" x 5 1/2"; Davenport, Samuel
    [Philadelphia ?] A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Aug. 11, 1876; 5" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], [Aug. 16, 1876]
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Aug. 19, 1876; 5 1/2" x 9"; Thomson, James
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Aug. 20, 1876; 5" x 8"; Thomson, James
    New Port,R.I., A.L.S. 3p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Aug. 24, [1876]; 5" x 8"; Thomson, James
    Staten Island, A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to Jno. L. Le Conte, Sept. 18, 1876; 5" x 8"; Grote, Augustus Radcliffe, 1841-1903
    Buffalo, A.L.S. 4p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Sept. 25, 1876; 4 1/2" x 7"; Ernst, C. W. (Carl Wilhelm), 1845-1919
    Providence, R.I., A.L.S. 3p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Sept. 26, 1876; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910
    Newport, A.L.S. 4p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], Nov. 4, 1876; 7x4-1/2; Lewis, George, 1829-1926
    A.L.S. 3p.,end. (see Le Conte papers.) Will exchange species, to get American insects.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Nov. 12, 1876; 5" x 8"; Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1837-1911
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, Nov. 14, 1876; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Mayfair, R. L.
    Algiers, Algeria, A.L.S. 5p. (see Le Conte papers.) Will welcome his friends. His interest is archaeology in North Africa. Describes James Bruce of Kinnaird and his preparatory explorations in Algeria. Friendly letter
  - Letter to [J.L.] Leconte, Nov. 14, 1876; 5" x 8"; Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1837-1911
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Nov. 20, 1876; 5" x 8"; McPherson, D. F.
    Princeton, A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Nov. 30, 1876; 7 1/4" x 9"; Smith, Robert Henry Soden, 1822-1890
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Dec. 7, 1876; 5" x 8"; Schwartz, Eugene Amandus, 1844-1928
    Detroit, A.L.S. 2p. End. in J.L.LeC's hand.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Dec. 12, 1876; 8" x 10"; Humphreys, A. A., (Andrew Atkinson), 1810-1883
    Washington, L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], Dec. 15, 1876; 9-1/4x5-3/4; Tiesenhausen, Alexander von, baron
    Trient, A.L.S. 4p.,end. In German. (see Le Conte papers.) Wishes to exchange insects.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Leconte, Dec. 29, 1876; 5" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Concerning the cost of maintaining the Dept. of Agriculture, 1876
  - Envelope addressed to [John L.] LeConte, from the Exoposition Égyptienne à Philadelphia, 1876
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], 1876; Bey, H. Brugsen
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], [1876]; 9x5-1/2; Bey, H. Brugsen
    Philadelphia; A.L.S. 1p. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Accepts his invitation.
  - Ticket of admission to Dr. and Mrs. [John L.] Le Conte, 1876; 2-1/2x4-1/4, 2-3/4x4-1/2; Philadelphia. Centennial exhibition, 1876
    Printed D. filled in in ms. 2 items. (see Le Conte papers.)
  - Letter to [John L.] LeConte, [1876?]; Barker, George F. (George Frederick), 1835-1910
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Jan. 2, 1877; 5 1/2" x 8 1/2"; Apgar, E. A.
    Trenton, N.J., A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], Jan. 2, 1877; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Retsima, C.
    Leyden, A.L.S. 1p.,end. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Asks for specimens of American insects.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Jan. 15, 1877; 5 1/2" x 8 1/2"; Mann, B. Pickman, (Benjamin Pickman), 1848-1926
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. Leconte, Jan. 22, 1877; 7x4-1/2; Lewis, George, 1829-1926
    London, A.L.S. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.) Thanks for the introduction. Will help him on Japanese entomology.
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], Jan. 27, 1877
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Feb. 4, 1877; 5" x 8"; Dall, William Healey, 1845-1927
    Smithsonian, A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Feb. 9, 1877; 5 1/4" x 8 1/2"; Dall, William Healey, 1845-1927
    Washington, A.L.S. 4p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Leconte, Feb. 12, 1877; 5" x 8"; Hagen, Hermann August, 1817-1893
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Feb. 17, 1877; 5" x 8"; Kane, Thomas Leiper, 1822-1883
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Feb. 19, 1877; 5" x 8"; Kane, Thomas Leiper, 1822-1883
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le conte, Feb. 23, 1877; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to [Rutherford B. Hayes], Mar. 6, 1877; McMichael, Morton, 1807-1879
  - Letters and documents to Rutherford B. Hayes recommending John L. Le Conte for the Position of Commissioner of Agriculture, March 6, 1877-[1877]; Nichols, S. H.
    D. 51 items. Various sizes. (see Le Conte papers.) For letter of Morton McMichael, see date of March 6, 1877. Originally B L493.2
    Unlocated: October 2010. (May possibly refer to unattributed collection of letters.)
  - Letters and documents to Rutherford B. Hayes recommending John L. Le Conte for the position of Commissioner of Agriculture, March 6, 1877-[1877]; Nicholson, Hunter
    Unlocated: October 2010. (May possibly refer to unattributed folder of letters.)
  - Letter to [Rutherford B. Hayes], Mar. 7, 1877; 8 x 10-1/2; Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia.
  - Letter to Rutherford B. Hayes, Mar. 7, 1877; 8 x 9-3/4; Columbia University.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, March 7, 1877; 8x5; Guyot, A. (Arnold), 1807-1884
    Princeton, N.J., L. 3p.with P.S.by Stephen Alexander. Copy. (see Le Conte papers.) Hopes he is appointed to head the agriculture section of the government.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, March 7, 1877; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Guyot, A. (Arnold), 1807-1884
    Princeton, A.L.S. 2p.and end.by Stephen Alexander. (see Le Conte papers.) Hopes he gets the post of commissioner of agriculture. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, March 7, 1877; 11x8-1/2; Mendenhall, Thomas Corwin
    Columbus, O., A.L.S. 2p.,end. (see Le Conte papers.) Will do everything to help him get the appointment as commissioner of agriculture. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [Rutherford B. Hayes], Mar. 7, 1877; 8 x 12-1/2; Society of Natural Sciences of Buffalo.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Philadelphia, March 8, 1877; 10x8; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Cannot recommend him for position of commissioner of agriculture, due to his position in the Smithsonian. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to the State agricultural society of Pennsylvania, March 8, 1877; 5" x 8"; Haldeman, Samuel Stehman, 1812-1880
    Chickies, Pa., Copy of L. 1p. and end. Recommending John L. Le Conte for the U.S. Commissioner of agriculture.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, March 8, 1877; 5" x 8"; Hilgard, J. E. (Julius Erasmus), 1825-1891
    Washington, A.L.S.2p. and end.
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], March 8, 1877; 8x5; Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1837-1911
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 4p. (see Le Conte papers) Has gathered signatures for memorial asking that Le Conte be appointed commissioner of agriculture. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [Rutherford B.] Hayes, Mar. 8, 1877; 8 x 9-3/4; Boston Society of Natural History
  - Recommendation of John L. LeConte for Commissioner of Agriculture, Mar. 8, 1877; 8-1/2 x 11; Haldeman, Samuel Stehman, 1812-1880
  - Letter to [Rutherford B. Hayes], Mar. 8, 1877; 8 x 10-1/2; Scott, Thomas Alexander, 1823-1881
  - Memorial to R[utherford] B. Hayes, [Mar. 8, 1877]; 8 x 12-1/2; University of Pennsylvania
  - Resolution recommending John L. Le Conte for the position of U.S. Commissioner of Agriculture, March 8, 1877; 5" x 8"; Zoological Society of Philadelphia
    Philadelphia, D. 1p. and end. Extract from the minutes.
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, March 9, 1877; 10x8; Riley, Charles V., (Charles Valentine), 1843-1895
    St.Louis, A.L.S. 2p.,end. (see Le Conte papers.) Recommends him for post of commissioner of agriculture, provided two mid-westerners do not get the post. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [Rutherford B. Hayes], March 9, 1877; 8x5; Rogers, William Barton, 1804-1882
    Boston, L. 2p.and end. Copy. (see Le Conte papers.) Recommends John L. Le Conte as Commissioner of Agriculture.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, March 9, 1877; 5" x 8"; Rogers, William Barton, 1804-1882
    Boston, A.L.S. 3p. and end.
  - Letter to [Rutherford B. Hayes], Mar. 9, 1877; 8-1/4 x 10-1/2; Flint, Charles Louis, 1824-1889; Rogers, William Barton, 1804-1882; Runkle, John Daniel, 1822-1902
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, March 10, 1877; 8x5; Gray, Asa, 1810-1888
    A.L.S. 4p.and end. (see Le Conte papers.) Lists reasons why the commissioner of agriculture should be a scientist, as the head of the Smithsonian is, and recommends Le Conte. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, March 10, 1877; 5" x 8"; Hilgard, J. E. (Julius Erasmus), 1825-1891
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, March 10, 1877; 5" x 8"; Marsh, Othniel Charles, 1831-1899
    New Haven, A.L.S. 1p. and end.
  - Letter to Rutherford B. Hayes, Mar. 10, 1877; 8 x 10; New York State Museum of Natural History.
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, March 10, 1877; 8-3/4x5-1/2; Sanborn, Robert H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p.and end. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning his possible appointment as Commissioner of Agriculture.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], March 12, [1877?]; 5" x 8"; Cuyler, John M.
    A.L.S. 2p. and end.
  - Letter to [Rutherford B. Hayes] recommending John L. Le Conte as commissioner of agriculture, March 12, 1877; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Cuyler, John M.
    L.S. 1p.and end. (see Le Conte papers.) B L493.3
  - Letter to F.A.P. Barnard, March 12, 1877; 8" x 12 1/2"; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    Washington, Copy of L. in J.L. Le Conte's hand. 1p. and end.
  - Letter to [Rutherford B. Hayes], Mar. 12, 1877; 8-1/2 x 11; Mendenhall, Thomas Corwin
  - Letter to Rutherford B. Hayes, Mar. 12, 1877; 8 x 12-1/2; New York Academy of Sciences.
  - Letter to the President of the U.S. [R.B. Hayes], March 12, 1877; 7 3/4" x 12 1/4"; Mendenhall, Thomas Corwin
    Columbus, Ohio, Copy of L. in J.L. Le Conte's hand. 2p.
  - Letter to Rutherford B. Hayes, March 12, 1877; 8" x 10"; Riley, Charles V., (Charles Valentine), 1843-1895
    President of the U.S., St. Louis, A.L.S. 1p.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, March 12, 1877; 8" x 10"; Riley, Charles V., (Charles Valentine), 1843-1895
    St. Louis, A.L.S. 1p.
  - Letter to Mrs. Helen G. Leconte, March 13, 1877; 8 1/2" x 11"; Grier, D. P.
    Peoria, I11., A.L.S. 1p.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, March 13, 1877; 5" x 8"; Hall, James, 1811-1898